<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fantasy Defense</string>
    <string name="tip_num">Tip _ : </string>
    <string name="tip0">Equip the item on your Hero under the [Item] > [Equipment] menu.</string>
    <string name="tip1">Clear stages and acquire up to 3 Heroes.</string>
    <string name="tip2">Certain stages reward you with a Hero character.</string>
    <string name="tip3">Use Mana to increase the levels of your Heroes.</string>
    <string name="tip4">Heroes consume Mana to use their special skills.</string>
    <string name="tip5">Special skills have a downtime after each use.</string>
    <string name="tip6">Clear a stage to receive Hero Points.</string>
    <string name="tip7">Configure your game settings under the [Title Screen] > Settings.</string>
    <string name="tip8">Basic units can be upgraded up to Level 3.</string>
    <string name="tip9">Hero units can be upgraded up to Level 5.</string>
    <string name="tip10">Upgrade your units to give them stronger abilities.</string>
    <string name="tip11">Use gold to advance your units to higher classes or increase their levels.</string>
    <string name="tip12">Increase the level of your units to improve their combat capabilities.</string>
    <string name="tip13">Advance your units to higher classes for more versatile abilities.</string>
    <string name="tip14">Reselling a unit returns to you a portion _ of the money that you spent to hire the unit.</string>
    <string name="tip15">You will fail a Boss stage if you fail to defeat the bosses.</string>
    <string name="tip16">Boss monsters have high HP, but they move slowly.</string>
    <string name="tip17">Monsters drop gold and mana upon death.</string>
    <string name="tip18">Use Hero Points to buy items under [Item] > [Shop].</string>
    <string name="tip19">Use Hero Points to upgrade your Hero and basic units under the [Skill] menu.</string>
    <string name="tip20">Knights, the 2nd advanced class of Warrior,_have high Attack Speed.</string>
    <string name="tip21">Warlords, the 3rd advanced class of Warrior,_inflict Splashed damage to multiple enemies.</string>
    <string name="tip22">Special Warrior Brandishers attack monsters with a chance of causing Stun.</string>
    <string name="tip23">Splatters, the 2nd advanced class of Archer,_shoot multi arrows and attack up to 3 enemies at the same time.</string>
    <string name="tip24">Sky Arrows, the 3rd advanced class of Archer,_strike enemies with their extremely Long Attack Range.</string>
    <string name="tip25">Special Archer Holy Eyes specialize in DoT (Damage over Time) attacks.</string>
    <string name="tip26">Sorceresses, the 2nd advanced class of Wizard, inflict Piercing damage.</string>
    <string name="tip27">Blasters, the 3rd advanced class of Wizard,_inflict Splashed damage with their Fire magic.</string>
    <string name="tip28">Special Wizard Ice Mages attack monsters with a chance of causing Slow.</string>
    <string name="tip29">Clear all the normal stages to unlock two special modes: _ Destroy the Moon and Infinite.</string>
    <string name="tip30">A stage\'s Infinite Mode is only opened_when you clear it with a perfect score.</string>
    <string name="tip31">The objective of Destroy the Moon is to destroy_the monster gates where monsters spawn.</string>
    <string name="tip32">Destroy stage objects to obtain gold and mana.</string>
    <string name="tip33">When clearing a normal stage more than twice,_you will receive only 70% of the Hero Point reward from the stage.</string>
    <string name="tip34">Touch a monster or object to manually attack it.</string>
    <string name="tip35">Blasters, the 3rd advanced class of Wizard,_inflict Splashed damage with their Fire magic.</string>
    <string name="tip36">Special Wizard Ice Mages attack monsters with a chance of causing Slow.</string>
    <string name="tip37">You will receive a Hero unit or additional ability_each time you clear 5 stages.</string>
    <string name="tip38">Clear Stage 25 to upgrade your units up to 10 levels.</string>
    <string name="tip39">Clear Stage 5 to unlock the special skill of your Hero units.</string>
    <string name="tip40">Clear Stage 30 to unlock the special attack ability_of your Hero units. (Splashed damage or Double Shot)</string>
    <string name="tip41">Never hesitate to upgrade your Heroes and basic units_when facing a difficult stage.</string>
    <string name="tip42">Certain stages contain special items for you to discover.</string>
    <string name="tip43">Cash items endow special abilities.</string>
    <string name="intro0">Humans and monsters used to coexist _ on the Crasto Continent,</string>
    <string name="intro1">and its history was determined by</string>
</resources>